Here Tim, let us discuss the other details that you have been commonly used for a method
attack us.
So, which I have observed, I may please experience, so I already mentioned there is a bit
submin.exe that was highly used by a threat attack for some time.
And you have seen the 32 little.exe, this task is used by the threat attack us.
So I have observed that CMD.exe also the threat attack will be used most of the time.
And the other common log-ins, log-as, which has been used, so which I have observed previously,
which will be the same as HTA we already discussed and Rich.exe also they will be using
the RDR leakage.exe to dump the Elsa's credentials.
From the mission, this one of the important log-ins, if you see in this kind of command that
has been executed by anyone that will be more harmful because we can able to dump background
shields from a machine by executing this command.
So the other log-as is like a PowerShell, they will be using the PowerShell to execute the
file as malware and some files and we will see this both of things in both of the log-as
not coming videos, so no need to about that.
So another one you need to think about the SS case so we can take a, we can by using
the SS case we can take a reverse connection from the target machine to attack our machine
so you have to be careful when there is a SS case just going on.
So this is the current shell dumping tools create dump.exe, so this is not a internal
it will be you have to download it from some applications, publications, then you can execute
this command.
So dump many tools also the same, this dump 64, everything of the central dumping tools
that it has been downloaded and they can perform some activities.
Yeah, these are the few log-ins that it has been commonly used with the titles to do
some certain attacks.
So let's talk about this video, I hope you have cleared understanding about the log-as
or what I was mentioning, so if you have, if you need to learn more about the log-as
that just do some research, the previous videos I have covered few of the log-as because
that was commonly abused by the detectors which I have seen in every attacks and every incident,
so I have covered what are the common are log-as that has been commonly used for the
detectors, so I know you will be familiar in there because you have seen up previous videos.
Okay, so see you guys a little bit, hope of this video and we will continue our discussion
in the next video, bye bye.